http://www.thehappycross-stitcher.com/pages/terms-and-conditions

1-35 *New Shades*
48 - 125 (variegated)
1-35 *New Shades*
48 - 125 (variegated)
OVERVIEW
This website is operated by The Happy Cross Stitcher. Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to The Happy Cross Stitcher and ‘you’ and ‘your’ refer to customers or visitors to the site.
By visiting our site and/ or purchasing something from us, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”), including those additional terms and conditions and policies referenced herein and/or available by hyperlink. These Terms of Service apply to all users of the site, please read them carefully. You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at any time at this page.
Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. To access their terms and conditions and Privacy Policy click here https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy
ONLINE STORE TERMS
By agreeing to these Terms of Service, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site. The website is not designed for children, we do not market children nor do we knowingly collect personal information from or about children. If you are under the age of 18, and wish to use this site please ask your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.
You may not use our site or products for any illegal or unauthorized purpose (including but not limited to copyright laws). You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.
In addition you must not use the site or products for (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; (c) to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information; (g) to upload or transmit viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the Service or of any related website, other websites, or the Internet; (h) to collect or track the personal information of others; (i) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (j) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (k) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Service or any related website, other websites, or the Internet.
A breach or violation of any of the Terms will result in an immediate termination of your Services.
GENERAL CONDITIONS
We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time.
You understand that your content (not including credit card information), may be transferred unencrypted and involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. Credit card information is always encrypted during transfer over networks.
You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service or any contact on the website through which the service is provided, without express written permission by us.
The headings used in this agreement are included for convenience only and will not limit or otherwise affect these Terms.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
Your submission of personal information through the store is governed by our Privacy Policy. To view our Privacy Policy click here https://www.thehappycross-stitcher.com/pages/privacy-policy
DELIVERY & DELIVERY CHARGES
All orders over £20 are delivered FREE of Postage & Packing to all addresses in the UK. Orders £20 and under are charged at £2.50 to cover post, packaging and credit card processing fees.
Postage and Packing to Europe starts from £3.95. Postage and Packing outside of Europe starts from £6.95.
Any Customs Duty is to be paid by the recipient.
Orders are usually dispatched within 7 days and we endeavour to despatch all orders within 14 days. If there is a delay on your order which will result in despatch after 7 days, then we will contact you to explain why your order will be delayed and give you a new despatch date. Should your delayed order contain multiple items we will despatch as much as possible and/or contact you to discuss the options.
If the delay is unacceptable to you then you have the right to cancel the order with a full refund.
If the item is a gift and you need it by a specific date please contact us before ordering so that we can let you know if there will be any problems.
PRICING
We accept payment in POUNDS STERLING ONLY (GB Pounds)
Cheques must be drawn on a UK bank.
Most major Credit & Debit Cards are accepted for online payments
Prices for our products are subject to change without notice.
VAT Number 324 2413 42
PAYMENT OPTIONS:
We accept most major credit/debit cards including Visa and Mastercard. Transactions are processed securely online through our preferred payment processors, Sagepay and PayPal.
All card payments are processed immediately your order is placed.
We also accept cheques/postal orders made out in British Sterling and drawn on UK banks or the Post Office.
CREDIT CARD SECURITY
All Credit Card and Debit Card transactions are conducted securely by Sagepay or PayPal. We keep no record of your card details
CANCELLATION OF ORDER
You can cancel your order from the date of the contract and up to 7 working days, starting from the day after you receive the goods. Upon cancellation we will return your money within 30 days of the cancellation, less the original postal costs incurred. You must bear all costs of returning the goods to us.
Please return the goods to:- The Happy Cross-Stitcher September Cottage 55 Haughton Green Darlington DL1 2DD United Kingdom
RETURNS
Our policy lasts 30 days. If 30 days have gone by since your purchase, unfortunately we can’t offer you a refund or exchange.
To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. It must also be in the original packaging.
To complete your return, please supply us with your name & address, invoice number and the reason for the return IN ADVANCE OF RETURNING THE ITEM(S), failure to do so will incur a £5.00 restocking fee. Please return to: The Happy Cross Stitcher, September Cottage, 55 Haughton Green, Darlington DL1 2DD, United Kingdom.
To return items from overseas please contact us first to make arrangements.
We cannot be held responsible for items returned and lost in transit. Please obtain either a certificate of posting from your Post Office or use a recorded delivery service
For our full Returns Policy click here - https://www.thehappycross-stitcher.com/pages/refund-policy
PHOTO TO CHART
The Happy Cross Stitcher Photo to Chart service produces a cross stitch chart from a customer supplied image and as such will be a clear interpretation but not an exact pixel for pixel replica of your image. For example, fine detail such as facial lines or multiple hair colours may not chart easily - in a photograph these may be constructed of single or multiple pixels, where as a single cross-stitch is actually quite large in comparison.
Our charts are produced to the highest standard, however the final charting can only ever be as good as the image provided.
You will be informed if we think the image will not chart satisfactorily and you will be offered the opportunity to supply an alternate image for charting or alternatively a full refund, otherwise refunds will only be given if an error is made during the chart conversion process. Please note that we ask that you obtain permission to use a picture or image where copyright issues exist. We are converting images on your behalf and cannot be held liable for any copyright infringement.
PRODUCTS
We have made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colours and images of our products that appear at the store. We cannot guarantee that your computer monitor's display of any colour will be accurate.
All descriptions of products or product pricing are subject to change at anytime without notice, at the sole discretion of us. We reserve the right to discontinue any product at any time.
NEWSLETTER
You may elect to join our mailing list and we will send you regular newsletters and details of special offers. You can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time by contacting us with your email address and unsubscribe request.
CUSTOMER SUPPORT
Please contact as follows:
Address:
The Happy Cross-Stitcher September Cottage 55 Haughton Green Darlington DL1 2DD United Kingdom
Business Owner: Danielle Armstrong
Telephone:
From UK: 01325 240192 (calls charged at UK national rates) International: 0044 1325 240192
General Opening Times:
Monday - Friday: 09.00 - 18.30 Saturday: 09.30 - 12.00 Sunday: Closed
Outside these times a telephone answering service is available. Please leave a clear concise message, together with your name and telephone number and we will return your call as soon as possible. Please note that this is an online store only and not a bricks and mortar shop.
GOVERNING LAW
These Terms of Service and any separate agreements whereby we provide you Services shall be governed by and construed in accordance with English Law.
